

Seasoned sales director with 10+ years'experience recruiting, training, and leading sales teams to consistently exceed revenue goals. Comprehensive understanding of stakeholder management and maintaining enduring client relationships. Adept at managing the sales process from prospecting to closing and seizing new growth opportunities.

Professional Experience

Enterprise Sales Director

Numerator, Las Vegas, NV July 2017 - Present

- Implement effective company policies to ensure that all practices comply with labor and employment regulations
- Increased employee retention rates by managing workplace satisfaction to an over 90% success rate by creating and maintaining a positive work environment
- Develop targeted outreach practices to increase minority recruitment and ensure compliance with affirmative action policies
- Monitor scheduled in and out times as well as employee breaks to ensure that proper employment laws are met

Territory Sales Manager

Celsius Holdings Incorporated, Las Vegas, NV June 2000- July 2017

- Worked collaboratively with regional managers to set team goals and identify new business opportunities
- Pla n n ed a n d del ivered profession a I deve lopm e nt sessi ons for sa les representatives to improve selling tactics
- Established and maintained professional networks and prospected for new clients
- Met with clients and used active listening techniques to gain deep insights into their needs and suggest valuable solutions

4759 Sunnydale Lane Plano. TX, 75071 email@youremail.com (469) 385-2948

Education

Bachelor of Science in Business Administration and Management University Of Nevada, Las Vegas, NV September 1994 - June 1998

Master of Science in Business Administration University Of Nevada, Las Vegas, NV September 1998 - June 2000

Key Skills

- Articulate negotiator
- Assertive and inspiring leadership
- Extensive knowledge of sales processes
- Relationship management
- Collaborative mindset